Finding Aid for the W.W. Robinson papers, ca. 1843-1972
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Biographical - photographs.
  - Group., 1957 Jul 21, Aug 17, Nov 1, Nov 21 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Groups., 1957 Jul 21, Aug 17, Nov 1, Nov 21; Publ Branding Iron no. 40 (1957 Dec): "Tin Star Night". (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Group., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Christmas party., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Biographical - photographs, publicity, business.
  - WWR and group of men., ca. 1959; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - WWR and Noah Lindsey Beery., September 1960; 1 photograph in Branding Iron, nop 54 (Sept. 1960). (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Westerners.
  - WWR and group of men., November 11,1960; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - WWR and group of men., 6 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - WWR and group meetings., October 18, 1962; 9 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - WWR and Walt Wheelock., July 20,1963; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - WWR and group., August 27, 1963; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - WWR., 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - WWR and group of men., March 10, 1965 and October 13, 1965; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Westerners at service form Robert J. Woods., June 1967; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Westerners - by Iron Eyes Cody.
  - $500 Reward photographs., ca. 1950s; 7 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - WWR, Elmer Belt, Gregg Layne, etc.., ca. 1950s; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Zamorano Club at Southwestern Museum.
  - Henry Wagner and Frederich Hodge at SW Museum., ca. 1950s; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - WWR, Lawrence Clark Powell,., ca. 1950s; 4 snapshots. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Southwestern Museum.
  - WWR in group shot., 1953; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Henry R. Wagners' 91st Birthday Party.
  - WWR, Robert Campbell, and Lawrence Clark Powell., Feb. 1949; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Rosenbach exhibit at UCLA Library.
  - Elmer Belt, WWR, Lawrence Clark Powell, other men unidentified., ca. 1950s; 8 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    UCLA Friends of the Library.
  - Lawrence Clark Powell, Mary de Wolfe and others in Special Collections at Powell Library., ca. 1950s; 6 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - WWR, Irene Robinson, Lawrence Clark Powell, Robert Vosper and other in Special Collections in Powell Library., ca. 1952; 12 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - WWR, Lawrence Clark Powell, etc.., ca. 1952; 8 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Lawrence Clark Powell's home gathering., ca. 1950; 4 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - UCLA Friends of the Library meeting., ca. 1950; 6 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 22)
    UCLA friends of the Library.
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., ca. 1950; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., 3 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    UCLA Library.
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., ca. 1950; 3 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Campbell Contest: Denis R Hussey, Paul Wellman, H. Richard Archer, WWR (judges)., ca. 1954; 4 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., ca. 1953; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., June 10, 1954; 8x10 BW- Friend's Day, WWR. (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., November 30, 1954; 4 photographs - Friend's meeting. (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - UCLA Friends of the Library., November 30, 1954; 4 photographs - Friend's new officers. (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - UCLA Library., 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Last Frontierman Exhibit - Sheriff Biscailuz, Lawrence Clark Powell, WWR in Powell Rotunda., June 2, 1957; 3 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Lawrence Clark Powell's open house Malibu., July 14, 1957; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - WWR and Robert Vosper., ca. 1955; 1 color print. (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Lawrence Clark Powell (Malibu House)., 1956; 1 color print and 1 bw print. (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - WWR, Robert Vosper,., ca. 1955; 1 8x10 bw print. (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - WWR, M. S. Slocum., 1950; 3 photographs and 1 negative. (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - WWR and group., 6 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 38)
    Santa Anita(?).
  - Ward Ritchie and group., ca. 1950s; 1 8x10 bw print. (Box 28, Folder 39)
    Ward Ritchie.
  - WWR and Irene., ca. 1950s; 1 8x10 bw print. (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Ward Ritchie home (gathering)., ca. 1950s; 4 proof sheets. (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - WWR with 3 men., 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - WWR with 3 men., ca. 1950s; 1 photograph. (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - WWR, Glen Dawson, Grant Dahlstrom, Lawrence Clark Powell., ca. 1950s; 5 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Group photo by Steve Birch., ca. 1950s; 3 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 45)
    The Optimists Club.
  - Graduation 1957. Honorary Degrees. Aubrey Wardman, Donald Bryon Spitter, and Preston Hotchkins., 2 8x10 bw prints. (Box 28, Folder 46)
    Whittier College.
  - WWR and Irene., 1964; 5 color snapshots and 1 bw snapshot. (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - LA Public Library Exhibit. Ranchos become cities., 1950s; 1 bw print and 1 negative. (Box 28, Folder 48)
    LA Public Library.
  - Lawrence Clark Powell's Malibu., ca. 1950s; 4 bw 8x10 prints. (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Mayor Yorty, WWR., ca. 1955; 1 photograph by Ben F. Grogg. (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Warrant Officer Robert Pearce and Rin., 1944; 2 photographs and 1 negative. (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - WWR, Irene Robinson, Leo Politi, Doris Gates, Ruth Gagbardo, Maguerite De Angeli at Sky Room, Wilton Hotel, Long Beach., May 24,1950; 2 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - WWR visiting classroom in grade school for Ranchos of the Spanish Dons.., ca. 1950s; 7 bw photographs (KNX Photo). (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - WWR. Photos by Frank Taylor., October 29, 1970; 6 bw photographs. (Box 28, Folder 54)
    Cultural Heritage Board.
  - WWR and Mayor Sam Yorty., ca. 1960s; 14 8x10 prints by Vanguard Photography. (Box 28, Folder 55)
  - WWR., ca. 1960s; 12 photographs. (Box 28, Folder 56)
    Lecture Bureaus.
- Oversize material, includes all groups.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Aguage Del Centinela., 1937 April 6 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    Agua de la Centinela - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on San Fernando Mission., 1937 Sept 8 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    Ex-Mission San Fernando - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho La Ballona., 1938 Aug 23 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    La Ballona - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Index of grantees, Rancho Los Feliz., No date / various dates; Magenta cover. (Box 98, Folder 4)
    Los Feliz - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Los Palos Verdes., 1929 Mar 22; 5 pcs. Includes 4 maps. (Box 98, Folder 5)
    Los Palos Verdes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Palos Verdes., 1929 Apr 3 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceeding on Rancho Paso de Bartolo Viejo., No date / various dates; Unbound. (Box 99, Folder 2)
    Paso de Bartolo Viejo - Ranchos, Los Angeles - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Rincon de Los Bueyes., 1938 Oct 8 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    Rincon de Los Bueyes - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Antonio., 1937 Sept 22 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    San Antonio - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Antonio., 1940 Nov 2 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Jose., 1936 July 17; Unbound. (Box 100, Folder 4)
    San Jose - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - San Jose de Buenos Ayres., 1937 Sept 8 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    San Jose de Buenos Ayres - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Patent to Manuel Garfias for Rancho San Pascual., 1863 Apr 3; 9 leaves. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    San Pascual - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho San Pedro., 1936 Bun 3 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    San Pedro - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings of Santa Catalina Island., 1940 Nov 2 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    Santa Catalina - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Tujunga., 1949 Mar 1; Letter from U.S. District Court. (Box 101, Folder 2)
    Tujunga - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Transcript of Land Commission Proceedings on Rancho Sausal Redondo., 1937 April 6 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    Sausal Redondo - Ranchos, Los Angeles County - Copy.
  - Rancho book, Orange County., No date / various dates; Black cover. (Box 101, Folder 4)
    General - Ranchos, Orange County - Copy.
  - [check]., No date / various dates; Some copies (photostats) from the Bancroft, other not identified. (Box 102, Folder 1)
    [Check] - Ranchos, Los Angeles County? - [Copy / copies].
  - Plate for illustration., No date / various dates; Labels in IBR's hand. (Box 103, Folder 1)
    Catalina - Books and Pamphlets - Publication material.
  - High school or junior high school graduation., No date; Mounted on board. (Box 104, Folder 1)
    Education - Biographical.
  - Wedding portrait., No date; In folder with signature [illegible] Williams. (Box 104, Folder 2)
    IBR and WWR - Biographical.
  - "Close cropped photograph of WWR." Cf. Hicks., No date / various dates; 2 prints, cropped differently. (Box 104, Folder 3)
    Hicks Bibliography - Biographical.
  - Diploma., 1916 May 15; Signed by Benjamin Ide wheeler, Harry R. Hartfield (?), and Governor Hiram W. Johnson. (Box 104, Folder 4)
    UC Berkeley - Biographical - Graduation.
  - Certificate of membership., 1937 Oct 16; Signed by Lindley Bynum, J Gregg Layne, Don Rogerio Felipe Dalton. (Box 104, Folder 5)
    E Clampus Vitus - Biographical - Organizations, Social - Membership material.
  - Award of Merit., 1960 Jan 21; Signed by George L. Harding, Donald C. Biggs, and Warren R. Howell. (Box 104, Folder 6)
    California Historical Society - Biographical - Organizations, Historical - Membership material.
  - Certificates of appointment., 1964 - 1970; No certificate for 1967. Most in blue folders. (Box 104, Folder 7)
    Cultural Heritage Board - Biographical - Organizations, Civic - Membership material.
  - Certificate electing WWR a Fellow., 1961 Jan 19 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Commendation., 1970?; Signed by Eddy S. Felman, president and Kenneth Ross, director, Dept of Municipal Arts. (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Commendation., 1970 Nov; Signed by Mayor Sam Yorty. (Box 104, Folder 10)
    City of Los Angeles - Biographical - Organizations, Civic - Outreach material.
  - Certificate of appointment., 1967 Aug 30; Signed by Governor Ronald Reagan and the Secretary of State. (Box 104, Folder 11)
    California Bicentennial Celebration Commission - Biographical - Organizations, Civic - Membership material.
  - Fowler, D.J. Outline of the history of the telephone in the United States., No date / various dates; In cloth boards, stamped Personal File D.J. Fowler. Also: Letter from Ann Walker to Fowler, 1928 Jan 16. (Box 105, Folder 1)
    General - Research Material - Various.
  - T.I.T. scrapbook., 1890s (late); WWR's note on contents with box. Early forms and publications, several 1896 - 1897. (Box 106, Folder 1)
    The Land and the People - Writings - Unpublished - Research / publication material.
  - Certificate of Honor from the Southern California Chapter of the American institute of Architects., 1930 Feb; For the building 433 South Spring. Signed by H.C. Chambers, president, and by the secretary. (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - T.I.T. scrapbooks., 1890s (late) - 1900s (early); WWR's note on contents with box. Some items (photographs) 1895, policy forms, notices, etc., ca. 1895 - 1901. (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - T.I.T. scrapbook., 1930s; Clippings about services and personnel, some with photographs. (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - T.I.T. scrapbook: Union Trust and Title Company historical material., 1900s (early); Newspaper clippings, copies of correspondence, etc. (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles research material., 1950s (late) - 1960s; Clippings from and issues of national magazines with articles about Los Angeles: Holiday, etc. (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - T.I.T. memorabilia and photographs., No date / various dates (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Harry Lancaster, Cambridge to Henry Carter, London., 1749; [Folders in map drawers 111 - 119]. (Box 111, Folder 1)
    General - Research Material? - Indenture [document].
  - Francis Ellis, Clifford, County of York to William Mountain, Thorp Arch, City of York., 1806 (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Folded map., No date; 2 cop. 1 damaged in lower left corner, the other complete but with bad fold damage and some foxing. (Box 112, Folder 1)
    The Old Spanish and Mexican Ranchos of Orange County - Miscellaneous? (Not in Hicks) - Publication - A map issued by Title Insurance and Trust Company of Los Angeles adapted from the 1946 official map of Orange County
  - Flat map copyright by G.T. Dicus, artist Fred Eddy., 1950?; Damaged, brittle. Dedicated to my good friend E.W. Biscailuz and all Californians, native and adopted. Signed: To my friend W.W. Robinson [indecipherable]. (Box 112, Folder 2)
    California: A Map of History - Research Material - Publication.
  - [Los Angeles, CA] :: Automobile Club of Southern California., [1932] (Box 112, Folder 3)
    A Map of Exploration in the Spanish Southwest, 1528 - 1793 - Research Material - Publication - Comp by Joseph J. Hill painted by Dillon Lauritzen for Touring topics, Automobile Club of Southern California
  - [Los Angeles CA] Westings., 1954 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    Outdoor Play Places of California - Research Material - Publication - A cartographic map of some of the outstanding recreational areas of the Golden State / designed by Lowell Butler; with descriptive notes by William Webb and Phil Townsend Hanna; drawings by Ken Sawyer; color by Harry O. Diamond
  - [Los Angeles CA] Automobile Club of Southern California., c. 1952 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    A Map of Marked Historical Sites of California - Research Material - Publication - Compiled from the registrations of the California State Department of Natural Resources, by Phil Townsend Hanna and William Webb; cartography by Lowell Butler, drawing by Gordon Brusstar, color by Harry Diamond
  - No title., No date, seemingly 1940s - 1950s; On verso, The California missions and Mission San Fernando [further history and chronologies]. (Box 112, Folder 6)
    Mission San Fernando [Chronology and Map] - Research Material - Publication.
  - No title., No dates / various dates; Ventura, etc. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    County Maps, Counties other than Los Angeles - Research Material - Publications.
  - Southern California no. 1., 1948; Ed. Of 1901 reprinted 1948. (Box 114, Folder 1)
    Geographical Survey - Research Material - Publication.
  - No title., No date (Box 114, Folder 2)
    Map of Los Angeles County - Research Material - Publication - Published by Hicks Borgnis
  - No title., 1866 (copy); Blue line copy. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    Map of the County of Los Angeles George Hansen - Research Material - Publication.
  - No title., 1877 (original); Blue line copies. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    Map of the County of Los Angeles Wildy and Stahlberg - Research Material - Publication.
  - No publisher given, modern copy in color, seemingly different from Dawson's reprint in MGI., No date on copy (Box 114, Folder 5)
    Map of the City of Los Angeles - Research Material - Publication - By H.J. Stevenson, U.S. Dept. Surveyor
  - No title., 1913; Mounted on linen, one fold remaining. (Box 114, Folder 6)
    Map of Los Angeles County (Southern Portion) - Research Material - Publication - And western portion of Orange County compiled from official records; published by the Barclay Map Co. Inc
  - Chicago IL?., 1930?; Cf. map in MGI. (Box 114, Folder 7)
    Rand McNally Map of Los Angeles County - Research Material - Publication.
  - No title., 1899 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    Rancho San Vicente y Santa Monica - Research Material - [Copy].
  - No title., 1898 May (Box 115, Folder 2)
    Rancho Rincon de los Bueyes o la Cienega - Research Material - Copy - Map of location of present dam
  - No title., 1883 Bun; Photostats. (Box 115, Folder 3)
    Rancho Boca de Santa Monica - Research Material - [Copy].
  - No title. (Box 115, Folder 4)
    Rancho la Puente - Research Material - [Copy].
  - Photograph (printed)., 1914 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    Bench and Bar of Los Angeles 1914 - Research Material - [Copy].
  - Portraits by Steckel., 1914 Bun (Box 116, Folder 2)
    Judges of the Superior Court, Los Angeles County, CAL - Research Material - Photographs (large printed).
  - "Retreat" Ord, Supply School, Camp Hancock Ga., 1918; Large panorama photograph in case. Housed in URL. Spencer Wyckof, Detroit MI. (Box 117, Folder 1)
    WW I - Biographical.
  - Los Angeles City map no.1., 1849; Printed copy, photograph negative print, photostat. (Box 118, Folder 1)
    Maps of Los Angeles - Books and Pamphlets - Research / publication material.
  - Los Angeles City, Pasadena, etc., 1877; Photograph print, geological survey map. (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles City abstract., 1857; Photostat copies, p. 31 - 34. (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Map of Zanja Madre, Los Angeles., 1888; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Maps of La Placita Olvera., 1870s; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Map of Los Angeles (Zanja System)., 1876; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Map of San Bernardino Meridian, Township no. 1., 1873; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Plat of the Place called Cuati., 1858; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Plat of the Ex Mission of San Fernando., 1858; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Map of Rancho Rodeo de las Aguas., 1869; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Various maps, plots and sections of Los Angeles., 1860s - 1870s; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Map of Los Angeles County, Abel Stearns' Ranchos., 1873; Photostat. (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Geological survey., 1938, 1932; 2 maps. (Box 119, Folder 1)
    Maps of Riverside County and San Bernardino - Research Material - Research / publication material.
  - Ranchos of Ventura County., 1951; 1 map. (Box 119, Folder 2)
    Map of Ventura County - Research Material - Research / publication material.
  - Ranchos of Santa Barbara County., n.d.; 2 maps. (Box 119, Folder 3)
    Map of Santa Barbara County - Research Material - Research/ publication.
  - Map of Historic Adobes., 1935; 1 map. (Box 119, Folder 4)
    Map of San Juan Capistrano - Research Material - Research/ publication.
  - From the North-East, Looking South-West., 1876; 1 map. (Box 119, Folder 5)
    Bird's eye view of San Diego, California - Research Material - Research/ publication.
  - Drawn b C. F. Otto Skobel., ca. 1864; 3 photostat copies of sketches. (Box 119, Folder 6)
    Map of Fort Miller, Fresno County - Research Material - Research/ publication.
  - Yolo, San Mateo, Santa Cruz, San Luis Obispo, Somona, Monterey and San Francisco., ca. 1860s - 1936; 8 maps. (Box 119, Folder 7)
    various map of counties, ranchos and mission adobes - Research Material - Research/ publication.
  - California., n.d.; 3 maps. (Box 119, Folder 8)
    Maps of California - Research Material - Research/ publication.
  - Clipping from: The Los Angeles Times., 1917 Nov 11; p. 14 - 15 and 23. (Box 120, Folder 1)
    A College Graduate in Search of a Job - Articles - Publication material - After commencement the deluge. By a recent graduate
  - Clipping from: California Southland, v.6 (1924 Jul)., p. 10. 2 cop. (Box 120, Folder 2)
    The Laguna Art Colony - Articles - Publication material.
  - Clipping from: The Los Angeles Times Illustrated Weekly., 1915 Sep 18 (Saturday); p. 9. (Box 120, Folder 3)
    Absolutely Hygienic - Fiction - Publication material.
- Research / manuscript material - by other writers.
  - Printer's copy., ca. 1957; Various pagings, ca. 300 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections and copy editing markings. (Box 127, Folder 1)
    Port Admiral - Publication material - Phineas Banning 1830 - 1885; by Maymie Krythe
  - Letters to WWR, enclosing the copy for review, etc., 1958 Nov 13, 1959 May 13 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    [Los Angeles County Courthouse]; by G. Arthur Waldron - Manuscript material.
  - [Copy]., 1959; 13 leaves. Typescript (carbon). Full title: Where and when was the first Los Angeles County Courthouse established?. (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - [Copy]., 1958; 1 preliminary leaf, 21, [2] leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 127, Folder 4)
    The Itinerant Search for a County Courthouse - Manuscript material - By G. Arthur Waldron
  - [Copy]., No date; 6 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 127, Folder 5)
    The Story of the Los Angeles County Courthouses - Manuscript material - By G. Arthur Waldron?
  - Hall of records; by W.W. Robinson., No date; 2 leaves total. Typescript (carbon). Unknown for what specific work. (Box 127, Folder 6)
    Los Angeles County Courthouse History / Histories - Research material.
  - List of minutes, Court of Sessions., 1960; Photocopy. Sent to Waldron. (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Copy., 1958 Sep; 8 leaves total. Typescript (carbon). Full title: Historical notes pertaining to the development of county courthouse (with references). Incorp. WWR's Hall of Records. (Box 127, Folder 8)
    [County Courthouses]; by G. Arthur Waldron - Manuscript material.
  - Newspaper clippings, etc., 1958 - 1959 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Bibliography; by Waldron?., ca. 1958?; Typescript (carbon). Typed notes from Bancroft, newspapers, etc. (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Typed notes., ca. 1958?; Typescript (carbon). From the Huntington Library, etc. (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Typed and photocopy copies of minutes, etc., ca. 1958?; Typescript (carbon). From Minutes of the Board of Supervisors, other Los Angeles documents. (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Typed and photocopy copies of minutes, etc., November 5, 1958; Photostat copy. Manuel Clemente Rojo vs Timothy Baldwin. Judgment Los Angeles May 20, 1850. Old Jail Lot. New Courthouse. (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Copy., 1966 May; ca. 40 leaves. Typescript (carbon). Student, CSUN? With note from Ms. Novak. (Box 128, Folder 1)
    The Andres Pico Adobe - Manuscript material - The story of an historical monument; by Pamela Novak
  - Letters from George Hammand., 1957 Nov - Dec (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Eulalia Perez Manuscript - Publication material.
  - Supporting documents, including portrait., Various dates; Photograph is a copy from the Bancroft. (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Copy., 1957 (translation); 5 preliminary leaves, 32 leaves. Typescript. Photograph is a copy from the Bancroft. (Box 128, Folder 4)
    Eulalia Perez Manuscript - Manuscript material.
  - Letter enclosing copy., 1968 Apr 14 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    Little Known Los Angeles; by Jehiel Shotwell Davis - Manuscript material.
  - Copy., 1966 (typing). ca; 90 leaves. Various processes, including typescript. (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Copy., 1954 Jul; 15 leaves total. Typescript (carbon). (Box 128, Folder 7)
    The Eagle Rock in Local History; by Glenn Price - Manuscript material.
  - Copies., 1931, 1932, no date; ca. 60 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 128, Folder 8)
    Three Talks by Morgan Russell - Manuscript material.
  - Copy., No date; 10 leaves total. Typescript with corrections. Comparisons of place names, Africa, California, Panama, etc. (Box 128, Folder 9)
    Our Lands of Mystery; by T. Cameron Taylor - Manuscript material.
  - Letter enclosing copy., 1969 Jul 19 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    Sarah Hathaway Bixby Smith; by Thelma Lee Hubbell - Manuscript material.
  - Copy., ca. 1968; 26 leaves. Typescript (photocopy). (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Letters from Ruth Moses, and the attorneys for EM., 1962 Oct (Box 128, Folder 12)